[EPIC]⚡ I can't believe our first day at MIT!
[EPIC]⚡ MJ, come on.
[EPIC]⚡ Pretend like you're not the happiest you've ever been in your entire
[EPIC]⚡ life.
[EPIC]⚡ I can't.
[EPIC]⚡ I knew it!
[EPIC]⚡ Hi, my name is Peter Parker.
[EPIC]⚡ You don't remember me, but we used to know each other.
[EPIC]⚡ Something bad was going to happen,
[EPIC]⚡ and the only way to stop it was to make everyone forget
[EPIC]⚡ about me.
[EPIC]⚡ Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
[EPIC]⚡ I'm Spider -Man.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Put your whimpering.
[EPIC]⚡ Suit yourself.
[EPIC]⚡ Go home!
[EPIC]⚡ And sometimes Spider -Man has to do the hard thing,
[EPIC]⚡ even if it breaks Peter Parker's heart.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 What is happening to me?
[EPIC]⚡ Excuse me, Dr. Banner.
[EPIC]⚡ I need your help.
[EPIC]⚡ What did you say your name was?
[EPIC]⚡ DNA is mutating?
[EPIC]⚡ Could be enormously dangerous.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Spiders have three life cycles.
[EPIC]⚡ When between cycles, it can leave the spider vulnerable to threats.
[EPIC]⚡ We are faced with a danger that we can't control.
[EPIC]⚡ One we can't even see.
[EPIC]⚡ Stay out of my way.
[EPIC]⚡ You're losing it, kid.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 And for those spiders who make it through,
[EPIC]⚡ it amounts to a kind of fever.
[EPIC]⚡ Nice flowers.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Oh, they're a housewarming gift.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I'm MJ.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I'm just a neighbor from across the hall.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 A friendly neighbor.